[{
        "Question": "Select question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
    },{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": "A grid-4 location and a grid-6 location are diagonal-with the grid-2 location. A grid-2 location is diagonal-with the grid-6 location. A grid-2 location is diagonal-with the grid-4 location. A grid-1 location is diagonal-with the grid-5 location. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the blue grid-3 location. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the grid-9 location. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the grid-7 location. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the grid-1 location. A blue grid-3 location is diagonal-with the grid-5 location. A grid-9 location is diagonal-with the grid-5 location. A grid-7 location is diagonal-with the grid-5 location. A grid-8 location is diagonal-with the grid-6 location. A grid-8 location is diagonal-with the grid-4 location. A grid-4 location is diagonal-with the grid-8 location. A grid-6 location is diagonal-with the grid-8 location. A black block is diagonal-with the black block. A black block is diagonal-with the black block. A grid-1 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-2 location. A blue grid-3 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-2 location is near the blue grid-3 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-6 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-1 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-1 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-8 location. A grid-5 location is near the blue grid-3 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-9 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-7 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-6 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-1 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-5 location. A blue grid-3 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-9 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-7 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-5 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-9 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-7 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-6 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-8 location. A grid-9 location is near the grid-8 location. A grid-7 location is near the grid-8 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-8 location. A blue block is near the black block. A black block is near the black block. A black block is near the blue block. A black block is near the black block. A blue grid-3 location is near the grid-6 location. A grid-6 location is near the blue grid-3 location. A grid-9 location is near the grid-6 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-9 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-7 location. A grid-7 location is near the grid-4 location. A blue block is near the black block. A black block is near the blue block. A grid-1 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-1 location. A grid-2 location is below the black block. A grid-4 location is below the black block. A grid-1 location is below the blue block. A black block is on the grid-2 location. A black block is on the grid-4 location. A blue block is on the grid-1 location."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is 'adjacent'?",
        "Answer": "If an object is not diagonal-with an object and the object is near the object , then the object and the object are adjacent."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is 'clear'?",
        "Answer": "If an object is not below an object , then it is clear."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the blue block?",
        "Answer": "A grid-1 location."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the black block 10?",
        "Answer": "A grid-4 location."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the black block 11?",
        "Answer": "An grid-2 location"
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-1 location?",
        "Answer": "A blue block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-2 location?",
        "Answer": "A black block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-3 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-4 location?",
        "Answer": "A black block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-5 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-6 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-7 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-8 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the grid-9 location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the grid-1 location?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the grid-1 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-1 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-1 location. A blue block is on the grid-1 location."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the grid-2 location?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. A grid-4 location is diagonal-with the grid-2 location. A grid-6 location is diagonal-with the grid-2 location. A grid-1 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-4 location is near the grid-2 location. A blue grid-3 location is near the grid-2 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-2 location. A black block is on the grid-2 location. "
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the grid-3 location?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is blue. A grid-5 location is diagonal-with the grid-3 location. A grid-6 location is near the grid-3 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-3 location."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the grid-4 location?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. A grid-2 location is diagonal-with the grid-4 location. A grid-8 location is diagonal-with the grid-4 location. A grid-1 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-2 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-5 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-8 location is near the grid-4 location. A grid-7 location is near the grid-4 location. A black block is on the grid-4 location. "
    }
]

